[Applause]
I've always had a passion of helping
people and this is why I'm really glad
that I'm able to help people optimizing
their processes I wanted to resale
myself because I was frustrated in my
old job and there was no perspective for
me to update my skills and uh so I want
to do something new as there's a
scarcity of it talent that was a huge
challenge for us finding and attracting
new people the journey has been amazing
really I think we started in the late of
Summer last year and needed only 2 weeks
to find the first employee after a few
months uh they was bable in our project
the most exciting thing to me is that in
business Central you have endless
possibilities you could use an API with
an AI model to improve business
processes what I like most about
business Central is that it's much more
fastpac than other VP solution it's the
entire team of the business Central they
really helped us to find people we
otherwise wouldn't be able to find and
then we ended up hiring six new talents
three consultants and three new
developers smooth sailing along the way
really a pleasant journey the most
surprising element for me was that there
are so many new hires from all around
the world I would recommend the resu
program to others to just step out of
the comfort zone I'm really glad that
this is my new job I see business Centra
as my canvas a place where I can craft
something truly EX
extraordinary as a Microsoft partner I
would say it's an absolutely no-brainer
to join the program as they can find you
great talents and bring knowledge not
only to those talents but also to your
company